Scandals after
you made it official
was not your fault
and the assault case
was mutually agreed
so it won't be a problem
But
President Goo was in
showbiz for many years
He's using the media
to ruin your image now
That's something
I have to take
Aren't you gonna regret
leaving showbiz?
I just wanna end it
as simply as possible
Of course
That's also what I want
By the way
you already got
a Christmas tree
Oh, yeah
Christmas is
around the corner
and I'll be working
on holiday
I just wanted to
get in the mood
Is that because of me?
Wait
I guess we don't need to
handle the public
It's gonna be buried
by itself
We hit the jackpot
[Choi Hyobum, Charged
for Illegal Drug Use]
[Multiple Injection
Trafficking Detected]
What would you
like to order?
A hot chocolate, please
Yes
Please credit reward
point to this number
I'll add
one iced Americano
Yes, ma'am
Shin Yoo-il is alone
in a cafe
near our agency
at the time Hyesung's
shooting is over?
I had business
around here
and I wanted
to give him a ride
Are you a man
with plenty of guts
or are you always so
devoted to your lover?
I don't know
I've never been in
a proper relationship